nugenix.com 2016-05-29

# Nugenix Free Testosterone | Privacy Policy

Welcome to the Nugenix website (www.Nugenix.com or the "Website"). This written policy (the "Privacy Policy") is designed to tell you about our practices regarding collection, use, and disclosure of information that you may provide via this Website and certain related services. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using, or submitting information, to this Website.

Policy

The policy of the Website is to respect and protect the privacy of our users. To fulfill this policy, the Website agrees to exercise the precautions set forth in this Privacy Policy to maintain the confidentiality of information provided by you in connection with accessing and using the Website.

Your Consent

This Privacy Policy sets forth the Website's current policies and practices with respect to nonpublic personal information of the users of the Website. By using this Website, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this Website, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. This Website is not intended for people under the age of 18. We never collect or maintain information at the Website from persons we know to be under age 18, and no part of our Website is designed to attract anyone under age 18. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose to websites.

Active Information Collection

Like many websites, this Website actively collects information from its visitors both by asking you specific questions and by permitting you to communicate directly with us via e-mail and/or feedback forms. Some of the information that you submit may be personally identifiable information (that is, information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your full name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number and sales delivery, billing and credit card information).

Some areas of this Website may require you to submit information in order for you to benefit from the specified features (such as newsletter subscriptions, tips/pointers, order processing) or to participate in a particular activity (such as sweepstakes or other promotions). You will be informed at each information collection point what information is required and what information is optional.

Disclosure of Information

We may disclose Personal Information to contractors or service providers that help us provide services to you or deliver products to you. For example, we will disclose your billing information to payment processors to process the transaction, we will disclose your shipping address to fulfillment and shipping contractors to deliver a product to you, and we may disclose your email address to email fulfillment contractors to send you emails from us.

We may share some or all of your Personal Information with our parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control, in which case we will require these affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas judicial proceeding, court orders or warrants served on us; or (b) to protect and defend our rights or property or the rights or property of third parties.

From time to time, we make the email addresses of those who access our Web site or otherwise provide and email address to us available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your email address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by calling customer care at 1-855-714-3234.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by entering your email at the unsubscribe page.

By providing my phone number, I provide my signature expressly consenting to contact from Nugenix or its subsidiaries, affiliates, or agents at the number I provided regarding products or services via live, automated or prerecorded telephone call, text message, or email. I understand that my telephone company may impose charges on me for these contacts, and I am not required to enter into this agreement as a condition of purchasing property, goods, or services. I understand that I can revoke this consent at any time.

We may disclose Personal Information to contractors, service providers or third party marketers that help us provide services, deliver products or advertisements to you.

If you would like to know (1) the categories of Personal Information that we disclosed in the prior calendar year to third parties about you for the purposes of the third party marketing and/or (2) the names and addresses of such third parties, please contact us at 1-855-714-3234.

Opt-Out Procedures

You may always opt-out of receiving communications from us. To not receive future e-mail communications from Nugenix, please go to www.Nugenix.com or contact us at 1-855-714-3234.

Security of Information

You can be assured that personal information collected through the Website is secure and is maintained in a manner consistent with current industry standards. The importance of security for all personal information associated with our subscribers is of utmost concern to us. Your personal information is protected in several ways. Your personal information resides on a secure server that only selected Nugenix employees and contractors have access to via password. In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third-party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Website cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party. Moreover, where you use passwords, ID numbers, or other special access features on this Website, it is your responsibility to safeguard them.

Passive Information Collection

As you navigate through a website, certain information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies and means, such as Internet Protocol addresses, cookies, Internet tags, and navigational data collection.

This Website may use Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP Address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider so you can access the Internet and is generally considered to be non-personally identifiable information, because in most cases an IP address is dynamic (changing each time you connect to the Internet), rather than static (unique to a particular user's computer). We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our server, report aggregate information, determine the fastest route for your computer to use in connecting to our Website, and administer and improve services to our consumers.

A "cookie" is a bit of information that a website sends to your web browser that helps the site remember information about you and your preferences.

"Session cookies" are temporary bits of information that are erased once you exit your web browser window or otherwise turn your computer off. Session cookies are used to improve navigation on websites and to collect aggregate statistical information. This Website uses session cookies.

"Persistent cookies" are more permanent bits of information that are placed on the hard drive of your computer and stay there unless you delete the cookie. Persistent cookies store information on your computer for a number of purposes, such as retrieving certain information you have previously provided (e.g., username), helping to determine what areas of the website visitors find most valuable, and customizing the website based on your preferences. This Website uses persistent cookies.

"Internet tags" (also known as single-pixel GIFs, clear GIFs, invisible GIFs, and 1-by-1 GIFs) are smaller than cookies and tell the website server information such as the IP address and browser type related to the visitor's computer. This Website uses Internet tags.

"Navigational data" ("log files," "server logs," and "clickstream" data) and "Internet Tags" are used for system management, to improve the content of the site, market research purposes, and to communicate information to visitors. This Website uses navigational data.

Links

This Website may contain links to websites of third parties not affiliated with Nugenix. This Privacy Policy will not apply to these third-party websites and the Website is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content on any of these other websites, even where these third-party sites indicate a special relationship or "partnership" with the Website. We do not disclose personally identifiable information to those responsible for the linked sites. The linked sites, however, may collect personal information from you when you link to their site. This collecting of information is not subject to the control of the Website. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policies of the sites you visit by linking from this Website.

Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may change over time. We will notify you by e-mail to the e-mail address associated with your account whenever we make any substantive changes to this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the changed version (for example, if you do not approve of a different way that we intend to use personal information) you may let us know by letter or e-mail. If you do not respond with any objections, we will assume that you consent to changes in the Privacy Policy. Changes will not apply retroactively to personal information that was collected before the changes to the Privacy Policy, except as may be required by law.

How to Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this site, please contact us at 1-855-714-3234.
